ISAAC ONYEMAECHI UGWU



Social Media Manager/ Digital Marketer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Amorji village Eziani Nsukka, 410002 Nsukka

amaechiisaac450@gmail.com, +23490115375399

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/Onyemaechi

Instagram: www.lnstagram/admin_cartwrightpromotions

Facebook: www.facebook/ProfCartwright

Portfolio: www.Portfolione.ml

EDUCATION

WAEC Sep 2017 – Jun 2020

Herald College, Nsukka

Digital Marketing Aug 2022 – Oct 2022

Lectera, Miami, USA

Certification in Digital and Social Media Marketing.

Degree Present

University of Nigeria Nsukka, Nsukka

Bachelor's Degree in Electrical Engineering.

Digital Marketing Sept 2022 – Dec 2022

AlephAds, Mexico.

Certification in Digital Marketing and Social Media Management.

Digital Marketing

SimpliLearn, England Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

Certification in Digital and Social Media Marketing.

SKILLS

Partnership Development. Social Media Management.

Social media Marketing. Customer acquisition.

Data analytics.

Marketing campaign development.

PROFILE

Expert marketing leader promotes record of leading successful marketing operations Creative and resourceful with high emotional intelligence. Oversees and contributes to highly effective campaigns. monitors performance and collaborates with teams to drive growth Stays on top of demands in fast-paced environments by effectively using slow periods Maintains organized clean and safe work areas with diligent attention to important details.

A dedicated professional with demonstrated strengths in customer service, time management and trend tracking. Good at troubleshooting problems and building successful solutions. Excellent verbal and written communicator with strong background cultivating positive relationships and exceeding goals.

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Manager

Present

Cartwright Promotions

- Researched advertising trends
- Developed projects to create content
- Published Digital Marketing content online
- Monitored Company Social media and Google Analytics
- Conducted market research to inform Ad campaigns

Digital Marketer

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022

Cryptocoingist

- Managed detailed campaign tracking across multiple channels and systems.
- Developed and implemented clear, consistent campaign strategies to drive growth.
- Created compelling and engaging content using social media, digital advertising, web, internal digital displays and more.
- Influenced high-visibility accounts and engaged target consumers with multi-pronged approaches.

Digital Marketing Specialist

CoinW, China.

Sept 2022- Present

- Researched advertising trends
- · Developed projects to create content
- Published Digital Marketing content online
- Monitored Company Social media and Google Analytics
- Conducted market research to inform Ad campaigns

Digital marketing Specialist

Digitmoni Fintech Solutions, Enugu Nigeria.

Sept 2022- present

- Researched advertising trends
- Developed projects to create content
- Published Digital Marketing content online
- Monitored Company social media and Google Analytics
- Conducted market research to inform Ad campaigns

Social Media Manager

Deeper Christian Life Ministry, Enugu State 2.

Jan 2023- present

- Researched advertising trends
- Developed projects to create content
- Published Digital Marketing content online
- Monitored Organization's social media and Google Analytics
- Conducted market research to inform Ad campaigns